<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-08-15T11:28:21+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">TROW</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">A day on top of greenery - Bonami Estate</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/13/bonami.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A day on top of greenery - Bonami Estate" /><published>2018-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/13/bonami</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/13/bonami.html">&lt;p&gt;It was a long dream of our office friends gang to go for a trip including stay. We were thinking about various places and available options but were confused. All the confusions came to an end when my flatmate Jishnu put some pics of Bonami Estate in our whatsapp group. I enquired the details, looks good for our team, a 3 bedroom old house with kitchen and cooking facilities at a rate of Rs.6500 for a day and that too on top of a tea plantation hill. We booked the same for a holiday friday !!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;location-bonami-tea-estate-near-vagamon-kerala&quot;&gt;Location: Bonami Tea Estate, Near Vagamon, Kerala&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arranged an innova crysta and started at morning 7’o clock. Our plan was to visit Thommankuthu waterfalls on the way and reach Bonami by evening. As planned we reached Thommankuthu at around 10 :00 AM, spend there some time. We could not get in to water because the entry to water was blocked. We started from there at 12.30 PM, had lunch from Thodupuzha and headed towards Bonami.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a rainy day and we were in Thodupuzha - Moolamattom - Vagamon - Bonami route. We bought chicken and cooking items from Moolamattom. After Moolamattom the road got narrower and the ascent started. There were small landslides here and there on the route, in some places people were trying to clear the way using JCBs. The raiin, hill &amp;amp; landslide - we got in to an adventures mood. We were very slow because of these reasons and it was already 5 PM. Fogs started blocking our vision and it increased when we approached Vagamon. The drive completely changed into a foggy one, there were no rays from the sun and we felt like night but the time was only 6:00 PM. Atlast we reached Elappara junction, where we have to take a diversion from main road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We called Raju, the contact person for the house. He directed us over call, the condition of roads changed, we couldn’t see anything around because there were no light. We met Raju and he pointed a yellow light on top of the hill, that was our house. We all got thrilled and finally reached the house by driving through tea plantations. It was very cold there !! When we looked around we could see some light at a far distance. The next house is miles apart, there were no disturbance but complete calm and cold climate. When we were settling down Raju arranged everything for us and left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an old traditional house with three spacious bedrooms having attached bathrooms in all, a kitchen and a sitout. Without wasting time we started preparing food. After having the dinner we  talked for hours by enjoying the cold breeze. It was very late when we slept, don’t remember the time, but we planned to wake up early to watch sun rise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I woke up hearing the sound of others, damn!! this time also I am late. But the happy thing was it was cloudy and raining outside. With rain fog came down and it was there for hours. We had hot tea and bread for breakfast. After that we had a walk through the beautiful tea plantations covered with fog. We enjoyed the foggy day by taking pics and walking through green hills. We spend time there till noon and started the return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was very hard to leave that place but there was no other option. We returned with a handful of memories , in my mind I was planning to come here again !!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It was a long dream of our office friends gang to go for a trip including stay. We were thinking about various places and available options but were confused. All the confusions came to an end when my flatmate Jishnu put some pics of Bonami Estate in our whatsapp group. I enquired the details, looks good for our team, a 3 bedroom old house with kitchen and cooking facilities at a rate of Rs.6500 for a day and that too on top of a tea plantation hill. We booked the same for a holiday friday !!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/carousal4.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Rain ride to Vembly Waterfalls</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/12/vembly.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Rain ride to Vembly Waterfalls" /><published>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-07-12T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/12/vembly</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/12/vembly.html">&lt;p&gt;Our friend Don came on a Thursday with an Instagram pic of Vembly waterfalls and at the moment I see it, we decided to go there. I checked with others, all were fine and we decided to go on the very next Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vembly Waterfalls or Vembili waterfalls is a beautiful waterfall situated at Urumbikkara near Mundakkayam, Kerala. It is around 11 km from Mundakkayam town in the Mundakayam - Urumbikara route, 25 km from Erattupetta, 37 km from Vagamon and 100 km from Kochi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location: Vembly Waterfalls near Mundakkayam, Kerala, India
Nearest Town: Mundakkayam (11km)
Nearest Airport: Cochin International Airport (108km)
Nearest Railway Station: Kottayam(63km)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our plan was to start at 7:30 AM from Kakkanad with 5 bikes and 6 people. Out of 6 people 5 of us are staying together and Don is not, so we decided to meet at Karingachira at 7:45 AM. But Saturday was a rainy day and it  ended in waking up late. Don reached the meeting point on time but we were just woke up. Somehow we started from our room around 8:15, but all were hungry so we targeted a restaurant first. Rain started heavily while we are having breakfast (Don still waiting for us). It was 9:00 AM, raining heavily outside but we decided to start anyway. Atlas we met Don around 9:30 am and started riding towards Vembly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We planned to go in Kakkanad – Pala – Mundakkayam – Vembly route and it was around 100 Km one side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ride through the curves in a line and that was just amazing. We reached Kanjirappally around 12:00 PM and Don took us to his Uncle’s house. He treated us very well, we had some hot black coffee and snacks. We spend some 15 minutes there and started again, one more hour remaining to reach destination. Atlast after 3 hours ride in the rain we reached the destination at 1:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no proper entrance or parking space because it is not an organised tourist spot. The waterfall loads only during monsoon seasons and the people from outside the place are not much aware of this fall. We had to walk around 60 meter through a private rubber estate to reach the fall. When we reached there we were surprised because no one else was there. When you are at an awesome fall and no one else is there other than you, what will you call that feeling? We felt like it was our own fall and we enjoyed to the maximum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rocks were very slippery but without thinking twice I started moving towards the fall and reached there, sat there for some time. When I looked up I was able to see water drops coming down and waterfall was spraying water on me. That was the first time I watched a fall this much closer. We spend around 2 hours there by looking at the fall, sitting on rocks, lying in water, taking photos and videos etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 3:00 PM we started the return ride. All were hungry because 2 hours in water fall and 3 hours ride in rain took away all our energy. We had the lunch from “Hotel Royal Park” restaurant in Mundakayam. It is a good restaurant and we all had a great lunch from there. While coming back we didn’t have any other plans, so we ride directly to flat. We reached back around 7:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a great ride and an amazing never before experience at a waterfall that will last in our memory forever !!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Our friend Don came on a Thursday with an Instagram pic of Vembly waterfalls and at the moment I see it, we decided to go there. I checked with others, all were fine and we decided to go on the very next Saturday.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/carousal1.png" /></entry></feed>